[
  {
    "id": "281",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In CloudFront you can have multiple origins in the same distribution?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "282",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "To restrict access to CloudFront distributions you can use which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "signed urls",
        "cookies",
        "restricted urls",
        "encrypted cookies",
        "IAM roles"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["signed urls", "cookies"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "283",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "To secure CloudFront distributions you can use which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "WAF",
        "Guard Duty",
        "Inspector",
        "NACLS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["WAF"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "284",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "By default, all newly created S3 buckets are _______?",
      "answers": [
        "public",
        "private",
        "undefined",
        "null"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["private"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "285",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "You can setup access control to your S3 buckets using which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "Bucket policies",
        "Access Control Lists",
        "IAM Rules",
        "IAM Policies",
        "WAF"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Bucket policies", "Access Control Lists"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "286",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you setup access control to your S3 buckets using bucket policies they are applied ________?",
      "answers": [
        "bucket wide",
        "granularly at the object level",
        "across all buckets"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["bucket wide"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "287",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you setup access control to your S3 buckets using Access Control Lists they can be applied ________?",
      "answers": [
        "granularly at the object level",
        "across all buckets"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["granularly at the object level"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "288",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "S3 buckets can be configured to create access logs which log all requests to _______ or to _________?",
      "answers": [
        "the bucket",
        "another bucket",
        "CloudTrail",
        "CloudWatch",
        "SNS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["the bucket", "another bucket"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "289",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "S3 buckets can be encrypted in which way?",
      "answers": [
        "in transit",
        "at rest",
        "both"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["both"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "290",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When S3 objects are secured in transit they are secured using which protocol?",
      "answers": [
        "SSL/TLS",
        "HTTP",
        "HTTPS",
        "KMS",
        "they can't be encrypted in transit"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SSL/TLS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "291",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "What are the three ways S3 objects can be encrypted server-side?",
      "answers": [
        "S3 Managed Keys - SSE-S3",
        "AWS Key Management Service managed keys - SSE-KMS",
        "Encryption with customer provided keys - SSE-C",
        "SSL/TLS",
        "HTTPS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["S3 Managed Keys - SSE-S3", "AWS Key Management Service managed keys - SSE-KMS", "Encryption with customer provided keys - SSE-C"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "292",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "What are the two ways S3 objects can be encrypted at rest?",
      "answers": [
        "server-side",
        "client-side",
        "customer provided encryption",
        "HTTPS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["server-side", "client-side"]
    }
  }
]
